[{
    "theme": "üõçÔ∏è Las compras",
    "langread": "en",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "What do you call a shop where you buy stamps or tobacco?",
            "answers": ["un estanco"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'postcards' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["tarjetas postales"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Where are the postcards?",
            "answers": ["est√°n al lado de las revistas"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you want envelopes for the postcards?",
            "answers": ["¬øquieren ustedes sobres para las tarjetas postales?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'stamp' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["el sello"]
        },
        {
            "question": "One stamp for Canada, please.",
            "answers": ["uno para Canad√°"]
        },
        {
            "question": "And one for Great Britain.",
            "answers": ["uno para Gran Breta√±a"]
        },
        {
            "question": "And one for Spain.",
            "answers": ["uno para Espa√±a"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say '4 euros and 30 cents'?",
            "answers": ["cuatro con treinta"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Have a nice day'?",
            "answers": ["que tenga un buen d√≠a"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'How can I help you?'",
            "answers": ["¬øen qu√© puedo ayudarles?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'We are just looking'?",
            "answers": ["solo estamos mirando"]
        },
        {
            "question": "If you need something, tell me.",
            "answers": ["si necesitan algo, d√≠gamelo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'shoes'?",
            "answers": ["los zapatos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'to try something on'?",
            "answers": ["probarse"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I would like'?",
            "answers": ["quisiera"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'His name is...'?",
            "answers": ["se llama"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'My name is...'?",
            "answers": ["me llamo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I would like to try it on'?",
            "answers": ["quisiera prob√°rmelo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I'm going to have a look'?",
            "answers": ["voy a ver"]
        },
        {
            "question": "We don‚Äôt have size 38.",
            "answers": ["no tenemos la talla 38"]
        },
        {
            "question": "It doesn‚Äôt matter.",
            "answers": ["no importa"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you like them? (Yes I do.)",
            "answers": ["s√≠, me gustan"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Are they OK?",
            "answers": ["est√°n bien"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'How much does it cost?'",
            "answers": ["¬øcu√°nto cuesta?", "¬øcu√°nto vale?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "She is taking them.",
            "answers": ["se los lleva"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'credit card'?",
            "answers": ["tarjeta de cr√©dito"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'passport'?",
            "answers": ["pasaporte"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'ID'?",
            "answers": ["DNI"]
        }
    ]
}]
